(Sheldon:)Thank you, Kripke...
(Sheldon:)...for depriving me of the opportunity
to share my news with my friends.
(Sheldon:)My pleasure.
-My thank-you was not sincere.
-But my pleasure is.
(Kripke:)Let me ask you a question.
(Kripke:)At what point
did National Public Radio...
...have to start scraping the bottom
of the barrel for its guests?
Eeh-eeh. Don't answer. It's rhetorical.
Well, why are you such a stupidhead?
(Sheldon:)That is also rhetorical.
(Sheldon:)I'm sorry you had to hear that.
Are you really gonna be on NPR?
(Sheldon:)Yes, they're interviewing me by phone
from my office...
(Sheldon:)...regarding the recent so-called discovery
of magnetic monopoles in spin ices.
(Sheldon:)It's pledge week, and they're trying
to goose the ratings with controversy.
(Leonard:)-Very cool. Congratulations.
-Thank you. My mother is very excited.
(Sheldon:)She's convening her Bible study group
to listen in...
(Sheldon:)...and then pray for my soul.